{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029848138","data":{"timestamp":" 947029848137"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 1da80645-0e2c-4693-8c60-51b351adc7d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" haraka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029856448","data":{"timestamp":" 947029856448"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 1da80645-0e2c-4693-8c60-51b351adc7d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" haraka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029858080","data":{"timestamp":" 947029858079"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 1da80645-0e2c-4693-8c60-51b351adc7d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hasira"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASIRA"," userResponse":" HASIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029861100","data":{"timestamp":" 947029861100"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 1da80645-0e2c-4693-8c60-51b351adc7d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hasira"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASIRA"," userResponse":" HASIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029862709","data":{"timestamp":" 947029862708"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 1da80645-0e2c-4693-8c60-51b351adc7d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029865587","data":{"timestamp":" 947029865586"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 1da80645-0e2c-4693-8c60-51b351adc7d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029867176","data":{"timestamp":" 947029867175"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 1da80645-0e2c-4693-8c60-51b351adc7d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hospitali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALI"," userResponse":" HOSPITALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029869723","data":{"timestamp":" 947029869722"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 1da80645-0e2c-4693-8c60-51b351adc7d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hospitali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALI"," userResponse":" START_HOSPITALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029871635","data":{"timestamp":" 947029871635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 1da80645-0e2c-4693-8c60-51b351adc7d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hospitali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALI"," userResponse":" START_HOSPITALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029873296","data":{"timestamp":" 947029873295"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 1da80645-0e2c-4693-8c60-51b351adc7d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hospitali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALI"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029874682","data":{"timestamp":" 947029874681"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 1da80645-0e2c-4693-8c60-51b351adc7d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hoho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HOHO"," userResponse":" HOSPITALI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029874933","data":{"timestamp":" 947029874932"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 1da80645-0e2c-4693-8c60-51b351adc7d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hoho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOHO"," userResponse":" HOHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029890377","data":{"timestamp":" 947029890377"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 1da80645-0e2c-4693-8c60-51b351adc7d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" hoho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029890479","data":{"timestamp":" 947029890479"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 1da80645-0e2c-4693-8c60-51b351adc7d1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hoho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOHO"," userResponse":" HOHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029905257","data":{"timestamp":" 947029905257"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" c938cee7-3e44-4b22-bc62-65cbd6bde441"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" haraka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029907881","data":{"timestamp":" 947029907880"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" c938cee7-3e44-4b22-bc62-65cbd6bde441"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" haraka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029909463","data":{"timestamp":" 947029909462"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" c938cee7-3e44-4b22-bc62-65cbd6bde441"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hasira"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASIRA"," userResponse":" HASIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029917575","data":{"timestamp":" 947029917574"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" c938cee7-3e44-4b22-bc62-65cbd6bde441"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hasira"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASIRA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029919185","data":{"timestamp":" 947029919184"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" c938cee7-3e44-4b22-bc62-65cbd6bde441"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029922062","data":{"timestamp":" 947029922061"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" c938cee7-3e44-4b22-bc62-65cbd6bde441"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029923665","data":{"timestamp":" 947029923664"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" c938cee7-3e44-4b22-bc62-65cbd6bde441"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hospitali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALI"," userResponse":" HOSPITALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029926804","data":{"timestamp":" 947029926803"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" c938cee7-3e44-4b22-bc62-65cbd6bde441"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hospitali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALI"," userResponse":" HOSPITALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029928414","data":{"timestamp":" 947029928414"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" c938cee7-3e44-4b22-bc62-65cbd6bde441"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" helikopta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029932275","data":{"timestamp":" 947029932274"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" c938cee7-3e44-4b22-bc62-65cbd6bde441"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" helikopta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029933879","data":{"timestamp":" 947029933878"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" c938cee7-3e44-4b22-bc62-65cbd6bde441"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hoho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOHO"," userResponse":" HOHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029936270","data":{"timestamp":" 947029936269"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" c938cee7-3e44-4b22-bc62-65cbd6bde441"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hoho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOHO"," userResponse":" HOHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029937908","data":{"timestamp":" 947029937907"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" c938cee7-3e44-4b22-bc62-65cbd6bde441"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEMA"," userResponse":" HEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029940994","data":{"timestamp":" 947029940994"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" c938cee7-3e44-4b22-bc62-65cbd6bde441"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEMA"," userResponse":" HEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029942622","data":{"timestamp":" 947029942621"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" c938cee7-3e44-4b22-bc62-65cbd6bde441"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" harusi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUSI"," userResponse":" HARUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029945497","data":{"timestamp":" 947029945496"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" c938cee7-3e44-4b22-bc62-65cbd6bde441"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" harusi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUSI"," userResponse":" HARUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029947104","data":{"timestamp":" 947029947103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" c938cee7-3e44-4b22-bc62-65cbd6bde441"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hujambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJAMBO"," userResponse":" HUJAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029949810","data":{"timestamp":" 947029949808"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" c938cee7-3e44-4b22-bc62-65cbd6bde441"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hujambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HUJAMBO"," userResponse":" START_HUJAMBO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029952033","data":{"timestamp":" 947029952033"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" c938cee7-3e44-4b22-bc62-65cbd6bde441"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hujambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJAMBO"," userResponse":" HUJAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029953622","data":{"timestamp":" 947029953621"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" c938cee7-3e44-4b22-bc62-65cbd6bde441"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" harufu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUFU"," userResponse":" HARUFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029956384","data":{"timestamp":" 947029956384"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" c938cee7-3e44-4b22-bc62-65cbd6bde441"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" harufu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUFU"," userResponse":" HARUFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029958405","data":{"timestamp":" 947029958404"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" c938cee7-3e44-4b22-bc62-65cbd6bde441"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" harufu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029958502","data":{"timestamp":" 947029958502"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" c938cee7-3e44-4b22-bc62-65cbd6bde441"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" harufu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUFU"," userResponse":" HARUFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029972157","data":{"timestamp":" 947029972156"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 78b588e8-5824-4238-8350-29d9ba3fce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" haraka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029974755","data":{"timestamp":" 947029974754"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 78b588e8-5824-4238-8350-29d9ba3fce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" haraka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" START_HARAKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029979218","data":{"timestamp":" 947029979217"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 78b588e8-5824-4238-8350-29d9ba3fce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" haraka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029980810","data":{"timestamp":" 947029980810"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 78b588e8-5824-4238-8350-29d9ba3fce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hasira"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASIRA"," userResponse":" HASIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029988733","data":{"timestamp":" 947029988732"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 78b588e8-5824-4238-8350-29d9ba3fce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hasira"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASIRA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029990334","data":{"timestamp":" 947029990334"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 78b588e8-5824-4238-8350-29d9ba3fce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029992916","data":{"timestamp":" 947029992915"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 78b588e8-5824-4238-8350-29d9ba3fce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947029994530","data":{"timestamp":" 947029994530"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 78b588e8-5824-4238-8350-29d9ba3fce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hospitali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALI"," userResponse":" HOSPITALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030000073","data":{"timestamp":" 947030000072"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 78b588e8-5824-4238-8350-29d9ba3fce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hospitali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALI"," userResponse":" HOSPITALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030001709","data":{"timestamp":" 947030001708"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 78b588e8-5824-4238-8350-29d9ba3fce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" helikopta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030005314","data":{"timestamp":" 947030005313"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 78b588e8-5824-4238-8350-29d9ba3fce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" helikopta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030006935","data":{"timestamp":" 947030006934"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 78b588e8-5824-4238-8350-29d9ba3fce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hoho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOHO"," userResponse":" HOHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030009376","data":{"timestamp":" 947030009375"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 78b588e8-5824-4238-8350-29d9ba3fce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hoho"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOHO"," userResponse":" HOHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030010980","data":{"timestamp":" 947030010979"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 78b588e8-5824-4238-8350-29d9ba3fce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEMA"," userResponse":" HEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030013149","data":{"timestamp":" 947030013148"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 78b588e8-5824-4238-8350-29d9ba3fce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEMA"," userResponse":" HEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030014772","data":{"timestamp":" 947030014771"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 78b588e8-5824-4238-8350-29d9ba3fce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" harusi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUSI"," userResponse":" HARUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030017751","data":{"timestamp":" 947030017750"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 78b588e8-5824-4238-8350-29d9ba3fce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" harusi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUSI"," userResponse":" HARUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030019369","data":{"timestamp":" 947030019368"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 78b588e8-5824-4238-8350-29d9ba3fce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hujambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJAMBO"," userResponse":" HUJAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030022312","data":{"timestamp":" 947030022312"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 78b588e8-5824-4238-8350-29d9ba3fce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hujambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJAMBO"," userResponse":" HUJAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030023916","data":{"timestamp":" 947030023915"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 78b588e8-5824-4238-8350-29d9ba3fce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" harufu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUFU"," userResponse":" HARUFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030026537","data":{"timestamp":" 947030026536"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 78b588e8-5824-4238-8350-29d9ba3fce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" harufu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUFU"," userResponse":" HARUFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030028574","data":{"timestamp":" 947030028572"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 78b588e8-5824-4238-8350-29d9ba3fce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" harufu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030028695","data":{"timestamp":" 947030028695"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 78b588e8-5824-4238-8350-29d9ba3fce50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" harufu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUFU"," userResponse":" HARUFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030041990","data":{"timestamp":" 947030041989"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8f83d4bd-b6a9-4eeb-8def-5ac9b72bf64f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" haraka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030044676","data":{"timestamp":" 947030044675"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8f83d4bd-b6a9-4eeb-8def-5ac9b72bf64f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" haraka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARAKA"," userResponse":" HARAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030046313","data":{"timestamp":" 947030046312"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8f83d4bd-b6a9-4eeb-8def-5ac9b72bf64f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hasira"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASIRA"," userResponse":" HASIRA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030054381","data":{"timestamp":" 947030054381"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8f83d4bd-b6a9-4eeb-8def-5ac9b72bf64f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hasira"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASIRA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030055977","data":{"timestamp":" 947030055976"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8f83d4bd-b6a9-4eeb-8def-5ac9b72bf64f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030065043","data":{"timestamp":" 947030065041"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8f83d4bd-b6a9-4eeb-8def-5ac9b72bf64f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030066642","data":{"timestamp":" 947030066641"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8f83d4bd-b6a9-4eeb-8def-5ac9b72bf64f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hospitali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALI"," userResponse":" HOSPITALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030073420","data":{"timestamp":" 947030073420"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8f83d4bd-b6a9-4eeb-8def-5ac9b72bf64f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hospitali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HOSPITALI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030075024","data":{"timestamp":" 947030075023"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8f83d4bd-b6a9-4eeb-8def-5ac9b72bf64f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" helikopta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030078134","data":{"timestamp":" 947030078133"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8f83d4bd-b6a9-4eeb-8def-5ac9b72bf64f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" helikopta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" START_HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030086236","data":{"timestamp":" 947030086236"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8f83d4bd-b6a9-4eeb-8def-5ac9b72bf64f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" helikopta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" START_HELIKOPTA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030088230","data":{"timestamp":" 947030088229"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8f83d4bd-b6a9-4eeb-8def-5ac9b72bf64f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" helikopta"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HELIKOPTA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030089829","data":{"timestamp":" 947030089829"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8f83d4bd-b6a9-4eeb-8def-5ac9b72bf64f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEMA"," userResponse":" HEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030095913","data":{"timestamp":" 947030095912"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8f83d4bd-b6a9-4eeb-8def-5ac9b72bf64f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hema"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HEMA"," userResponse":" HEMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030097529","data":{"timestamp":" 947030097528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8f83d4bd-b6a9-4eeb-8def-5ac9b72bf64f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" harusi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUSI"," userResponse":" HARUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030102423","data":{"timestamp":" 947030102423"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8f83d4bd-b6a9-4eeb-8def-5ac9b72bf64f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" harusi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUSI"," userResponse":" HARUSI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030104030","data":{"timestamp":" 947030104029"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8f83d4bd-b6a9-4eeb-8def-5ac9b72bf64f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hujambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJAMBO"," userResponse":" HUJAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030107380","data":{"timestamp":" 947030107379"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8f83d4bd-b6a9-4eeb-8def-5ac9b72bf64f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hujambo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUJAMBO"," userResponse":" HUJAMBO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030109001","data":{"timestamp":" 947030109000"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8f83d4bd-b6a9-4eeb-8def-5ac9b72bf64f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" harufu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUFU"," userResponse":" HARUFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030111775","data":{"timestamp":" 947030111775"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8f83d4bd-b6a9-4eeb-8def-5ac9b72bf64f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" harufu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUFU"," userResponse":" HARUFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-H.rand.47","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030113803","data":{"timestamp":" 947030113802"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8f83d4bd-b6a9-4eeb-8def-5ac9b72bf64f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" harufu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030113930","data":{"timestamp":" 947030113930"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8f83d4bd-b6a9-4eeb-8def-5ac9b72bf64f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-H.rand.47"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" harufu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HARUFU"," userResponse":" HARUFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.92","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030132845","data":{"timestamp":" 947030132845"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8c3e7885-ce3e-4a66-a74a-1540c28d7eac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.92"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-p-k"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.92","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030135958","data":{"timestamp":" 947030135958"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8c3e7885-ce3e-4a66-a74a-1540c28d7eac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.92"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-y-k"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.92","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030139841","data":{"timestamp":" 947030139840"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8c3e7885-ce3e-4a66-a74a-1540c28d7eac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.92"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_r-g-h"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.92","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030143644","data":{"timestamp":" 947030143644"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8c3e7885-ce3e-4a66-a74a-1540c28d7eac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.92"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_ch-h-m"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.92","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030146751","data":{"timestamp":" 947030146751"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8c3e7885-ce3e-4a66-a74a-1540c28d7eac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.92"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-ch-y"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.92","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030150735","data":{"timestamp":" 947030150735"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8c3e7885-ce3e-4a66-a74a-1540c28d7eac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.92"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-l-u"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.92","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030154744","data":{"timestamp":" 947030154744"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8c3e7885-ce3e-4a66-a74a-1540c28d7eac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.92"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_z-t-h"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.92","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030166901","data":{"timestamp":" 947030166901"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8c3e7885-ce3e-4a66-a74a-1540c28d7eac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.92"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_b-h-r"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.92","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030171056","data":{"timestamp":" 947030171055"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8c3e7885-ce3e-4a66-a74a-1540c28d7eac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.92"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_m-l-h"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.92","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030175629","data":{"timestamp":" 947030175629"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8c3e7885-ce3e-4a66-a74a-1540c28d7eac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.92"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-z-u"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.92","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030181401","data":{"timestamp":" 947030181399"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8c3e7885-ce3e-4a66-a74a-1540c28d7eac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.92"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-z-u"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947030229512","data":{"timestamp":" 947030229511"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_025020"," gameId":" 8c3e7885-ce3e-4a66-a74a-1540c28d7eac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_H..H.all.rand.all.stat.show.92"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_h_h-z-u"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}